<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/2018/06/18/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/18/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Emiliana Delgado, I’m from Caracas, Venezuela. I’m currently a student at Bentley University, majoring in Economics-Finance and also pursuing a liberal arts degree in Global Perspectives. I also have a minor in Entrepreneurship. I’m very interested in politics, economics, and technology.
My hobbies include jogging, playing tennis, snowboarding, hanging out with my friends, and watching every movie and TV show on Netflix.
My favorite food is pasta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My R package</title>
      <link>/2018/06/18/my-r-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/18/my-r-package/</guid>
      <description>The R package me and Abigail created is called TrainTest. The package makes it possible to use a function called “train_test()”, which takes in a csv file from the current R project folder you are using in quotes (ex: “file_name.csv”), the train set percentage, and the test set percentage. The function reads the csv file and creates a train and test set from the specified percentages. The output is a list where the first index returns the training set and the second index refers to the testing set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My top Kaggle submission</title>
      <link>/2018/06/18/my-top-kaggle-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/18/my-top-kaggle-submission/</guid>
      <description>My top Kaggle submission was made using a linear regression model. I selected the variables that seemed more important after reading what each one meant. Then I found a kernel in Kaggle that mentioned the weight that each variable contributed to getting the correct prediction, so I added some of the most important variables mentioned there as well.
I faced a problem when I tried to include some variables such as EXT_SOURCE_2 because it had a lot of missing values.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>